In the demon world lived evil beings
who followed their evil intentions
and were infatuated with destruction
and violence... known as demons.
Then there was the one who
desired to use violence and power to
bring these demons under his
command... the Demon King Ahriman.
That desire led him to try to bring all
of the demon world under his control.
And so, the invasion of
the demon king's army began!
Obey... the demon king!
Obey the demon king!
The demon king displayed his
overwhelmingly colossal power
as he laid waste to the demon world,
which brought fear to both
the human world and heaven.
It was only a matter of time before the
demon world was brought under one rule.
It was believed that this evil invasion
would soon spread to
the other worlds as well, but...
Impossible! My elite guard was taken
down by a single strike...
I am the demon king's right hand, Jahi.
Demon of the north, surrender to our army.
You're the demon king's...
Wh-What?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Why did you suddenly withdraw our forces
and stop our plans for
world domination, my lord?!
This is a grave matter, Jahi.
If we do not take care of this obstacle,
I cannot even think about the invasion.
An obstacle so great that
you've stopped your invasion?
What could it be?
Well...
Doux is... My daughter is just too kind!
What?
THE DEMON KING'S DAUGHTER IS TOO KIND!!
"The Demon King's Daughter is Too Kind!!"
Lady Doux is too kind?
Er, by Lady Doux, you of course mean...
My daughter that you are very familiar with.
Lady Doux...
It is true that Lady Doux
has always been quite kind
and gentle for a demon
ever since she was born...
That's only due to her
still being quite young.
It's only a matter of time until
she awakens to her true ruthless nature.
That's what I believed, as well.
But over the past six months
while you were gone on your campaign...
Doux's kindness has just gone too far!
She healed a human slave's wounds,
she helped some demon slaves carry things,
and shared some of her snacks
with some slave children!
And...
Papa!
Ah, Doux!
Look, it's a Mr. Lizard!
I saved him from the river!
Ah, is that so?
But don't get too close to the
river on your own, all right?
Okay!
As you can see, she'll save even a lizard.
L-Lady Doux...
Ah, Big Sister Jahi! Welcome back!
Y-Yes, I just returned...
My duties as a father come
before my duties as a king.
I'm so worried about Doux that I
can't even think about our invasion.
Your Majesty...
Very well.
Then I... shall train Lady Doux and
turn her into a ruthless, evil demon!
Is that so?
Ruthless?
Lady Doux.
I shall guide you into becoming a true demon.
That means we can play together, right?
No, there will be no "playing" involved.
I know that she is in good hands with you.
So, what exactly are you going to do?
Yes.
First, I will have her torture some weakling
humans and awaken her instincts as a demon.
To do so, we shall traverse the dense
forest that leads into the human world.
There are still many lawless, stray demons
within the forest that still us,
so I shall have Lady Doux also defeat—
Huh?
Be careful out there.
I'm gonna go play with Big Sister Jahi!
This is a problem.
I'm certain that Lady Doux can't shake her
kindness because the demon king spoils her so.
But I will not be spoiling her.
Lady Doux! Prepare yourself!
Wait, huh?
Lady Doux? Where did you go?
Did a stray demon get to her?!
Come get me!
She's safe!
"A FUN GAME OF HIDE-AND-SEEK"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: RYOTA TESHIMA
SONG: DOUX
Playing hide-and-seek with
Big Sister in the forest
Fun, fun hide-and-seek
Are you ready? (Are you ready?)
Not just yet (Not just yet)
Come here, come here now, and let's play
Playing even more
hide-and-seek with Big Sister
The birdies and bunnies are
also playing hide-and-seek
Are you ready? (Are you ready?)
Not just yet (Not just yet)
Everyone, come here and let's play
Aw, you found me! Okay, Doux will be it next.
We're not playing hide-and-seek!
Please listen.
Demons steal, oppress, and kill!
Those are the three principles we live by!
We have no time for these games.
Please understand that... Lady Doux?
Eat up, okay?
What did I just tell you?!
They looked hungry
so I gave them some treats!
Children are just so unpredictable...
Look at that weak-looking demon over there.
You'll be my dinner tonight!
We're splitting the goods, partner!
Silence.
You outlaws... who do you
think you're talking to?
You're next...
Your head's all bald, mister!
Do you like it?
Huh? Where'd Mr. Demon go?
I had it all wrong.
She didn't get like this
because she was spoiled.
She was born too kind!
And her softness rubs off
on everyone around her.
Even beasts or demons...
She's too dangerous. Her powers will
eventually destroy evil itself.
I must steel my resolve.
Ah! I found Mr. Demon!
We are not playing hide-and-seek!
We will now perform one of the
three principles of being a demon.
We will steal.
We will threaten the humans of
this village and steal their food.
That is the trial I am giving to you.
Do you know what threaten means, my lady?
Yup!
Then, go forth!
Okay! Off I go!
At this rate, not only will she not
be able to succeed the demon king...
she may not be able to live as a demon at all.
But she's the demon king's daughter.
When it comes down to it, I'm sure she'll...
Hi, lady! Can I have a sweet potato, please?
Are you shopping?!
Sure, coming right up.
I told you to steal it! I thought
you memorized your lines!
Yes! The cue card! We can
still turn this around!
I... I am a great demon.
Y-You pitiful and foolish humans.
I-If you do not give me an offering,
I will rip apart your flesh, set your
bowels on fire, and send you into madness.
My, my. Are you pretending to
be a demon in this day and age?
Look at those cute little
horns you put on your head.
We're doomed.
Here you go.
Oh, but I don't have any money.
You're stealing it, aren't
you? I don't need any money.
I injured my legs really badly a while back.
The doctor said I wouldn't
be able to stand ever again.
On top of that, the veggies this
year just didn't turn out well
and I can't seem to get any customers,
so I was planning to close my shop.
So if you'll have something like this...
Oh?
What's the matter? Are you not feeling well?
Stand up!
Hey, were you even listening?
I told you. I can't stand up... Huh?
M-My legs move.
How did...
How did this happen?
I'll come by to steal from
you every day, okay?
So make sure you stay healthy forever!
Yes, of course.
I guess I'm going to have to prepare
some offerings for you every day.
Um... c-carry on!
I stole it!
Why are you acting so smug?!
Helping a human with magic is
most unbecoming as a demon!
It would've been more effective if
you threatened her and stole it!
Yup! But...
I learned that you can get
things by helping others, too.
Doux wants to be a demon who helps everyone!
Th-That will never be allowed...
GUUUURGLE
Halfsies!
Doux! I've come to pick you up!
Ah, Papa! Halfsies!
Isn't it yummy, Papa?
Anything you give me is delicious, my love!
How am I supposed to win?
THE DEMON KING'S DAUGHTER HELPS TOO MUCH!!
"The Demon King's Daughter Helps Too Much!!"
Hey!
Hey, are you coming to pick her up?
Tell her to come by my place next time.
Pardon me.
Welcome, Jahi.
Th-Thank you for looking
after Lady Doux again today.
Lady Doux, what's this?
Big Sister Jahi!
Little Doux said she wanted to make some
dolls, so we've been making them together.
Doux's making the face!
You two have helped me so much,
but this is about all I can do.
Grammy is amazing!
Doux can't do this well on her own!
Well, then let's do our best together.
Okay!
What?!
You're helping some old
human woman every day?!
Yup! The grammy who gave me sweet potatoes.
Jahi, what is the meaning of this?!
You're even wearing a disguise!
Fear not, Your Majesty.
This is merely a trial to
entrap that old woman!
Oh?
In order to eventually deceive,
betray, and entrap that woman,
we are merely pretending to help those
people so we can gain their trust.
Thankfully, it appears that old woman
doesn't realize that Lady Doux is a demon
so it was child's play to lure her in.
I see. So that's what's going on!
Then I have just the thing.
Here you are.
Is that... salt?
Take one lick.
Y-Yes, Your Majesty.
Don't move.
Well? You can't move, can you?
Wh-What is this?
That is Puppet Salt.
If any living creature has a taste of that,
they will temporarily be forced to
follow any command from another.
Wh-Why did you use that on me?
To help kindle Doux's desire for domination.
Now, Doux. Go ahead and give Jahi an order.
An order?
Wha?!
She'll do anything you say.
Anything?
Yes. No matter how cruel
or horrifying it may be.
Okay, then...
ORDERS
HOLD ME + PAT ME ON THE HEAD
The demon king truly is terrifying.
Huh? What was that?
N-Nothing.
Now, Lady Doux.
Please make this the last time you
order me to do something like this.
But the effects are truly remarkable.
With this, she'll surely be able to...
Make sure you give that old
woman a cruel order!
Yup! Papa taught me a bunch of
cruel orders, so don't worry!
ANOTHER CUE CARD
Then go, my lady.
Okay!
With how much that old woman trusts Lady Doux,
she should have no issue putting
that Puppet Salt in her mouth.
Then we will betray her trust and
throw her into the depths of despair.
Here you go!
And then this trial will be complete...
Wait, why are you helping her
without hesitation, Lady Doux?!
This just means I must properly guide her...
Oh, Jahi.
Huh?
Could you come give me a hand?
Sure!
M-My body's moving on its own!
You're a lifesaver!
Yay!
This way, lady!
Sorry about this. We just
didn't have enough people.
The effects haven't worn off.
More importantly, this stuff makes
me follow human orders, too?!
Are you sure it's not defective?!
Can I put this here?
Yes, thank you.
Why are you taking stuff out of the house?
It's been decades since my house was built,
so the floors and walls are falling apart.
I decided to have it remodeled.
I'm going to be staying at a friend's place
in the meantime, so I'm taking my stuff out.
So you're going away?
Don't you worry. My friend's house and
my new home are both in this village.
But I have one request for you, Doux.
Wow! So many plushies!
Did you make all of these, Grammy?
I did.
And I want you to have all
of these little ones, Doux.
Huh? You're not taking them with you?
I'm not.
You don't want them anymore?
That's not true.
All this time, I've dusted them every day,
washed them, and sewed them back together.
So they're very, very important to me. But...
The ones who played
with them are gone now.
I'm sure these little ones would be happier
with you than with an old woman like me.
That's not true.
Huh?
Just watch.
Thank you so much!
Is Lady Doux doing okay?!
Move!
Th-The plushies moved?!
Yay!
H-How did this happen?
How?
I thought Puppet Salt was only
supposed to work on living things.
You're the first one I made...
See? I knew it!
They're all saying they want
to stay with you, Grammy!
Doux would've taken really
good care of them, too,
but the plushies want to stay with
the person who took care of them the most!
Could it be that...
Lady Doux's kindness awakened the souls
of these lifeless plushies?
My little ones...
So you keep them, Grammy!
That's Doux's order!
Doux... Well, if it's an order,
I guess I'll have to follow it.
I may be old, but I'd love
to keep you by my side.
Now and forever.
So, Jahi. How did the trial go—
What's the meaning of this?
Papa! Look!
This is my puppet!
I made it with Grammy!
Oho, look how cute it is!
Well done! What a good girl!
Next, I'm gonna make one for you, Papa!
I'm the luckiest papa in the world!
I'm so powerless.
I know. I'll go back out to the battlefield
and take the heads of some enemies.
Big Sister Jahi!
Lady Doux. What's this?
That's yours, Big Sister!
Now, we match!
Lady Doux...
Looks like you two have grown quite close.
I am trusting you to continue
looking after my precious Doux.
Huh? No, I...
Yes! I will be happy to!
Wait, the effects still haven't worn off.
Let's play again tomorrow, Big Sister.
B-But I need to...
Y-Yes. Nothing would make me happier...
Yay! I get to be with Big Sister!
Good for you, Doux.
Together! Together with Big Sister!